fι	ınction progress(){
	if (skill_matched == True){
	console.log("Selected");
	}
	else{
	console.log("God bless the company");
	}
١.	

Pooja Chaudhary

Frontend Engineer

My Contact

poojachaudhary831@gmail.com

+91 8077836237

(7) https://github.com/pooja-chaudhary

ที่กิ www.linkedin.com/in/ch-pooja

https://pooja-chaudhary.github.io/

Technical Skills

- HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery
- Bootstrap, React.js
- · Node.js, EJS
- SQL, MangoDB, Git

Other Skills

- Insurance and other financial products knowledge
- Investments
- · Products Pitching and selling
- Good communication skills

Education Background

- Meerut Institute of Engineering & Technology
 B.tech in Computer Science
 Completed in 2017
- Mahamaya Inter College
 Secondary Education pursued in science and maths.

•

Completed in 2013

About Me

Dedicated and detail-oriented Frontend Engineer with 2 years of experience. Eager to apply my skills in Developing beautiful and user friendly websites across the devices also having knowledge of backend tools, framework and database like SQL and MongoDB.

Professional Experience

Vueron Systems Private Limited / Frontend Engineer

Mar 2022- Till date

- Key responsibilities:
- Developing desktop and mobile friendly websites for clients using ReactJS, Javascript, CSS/HTML
- Implementing JQuery for refactoring the codebase
- · Cordination with UX Designers to build the websites

Vueron Systems Private Limited / Frontend Intern

Oct 2021- Mar 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Worked on Javascript, CSS/HTML along with ReactJS
- Rapid prototyping of small scale server with NodeJS and MongoDB

Hdfc Life Insurance company/Senior Corporate Agency Manager

2018 - 2021

- Key responsibilities:
- Managing and Serving Hdfc Bank customers
- identifying customers financial needs and suggesting financial instruments
- Managing customer portfolios

Research Paper

 Calculate the score of a social media profile and posts on twitter and other social media sites on the internet, Advances in Computers and Electronics, 2021